{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Answer these questions about the music of the 1970's.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Disco",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What genre of music was exemplified by \"The Hustle\" and \"Stayin' Alive\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "ABBA",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What popular pop group came from Sweden?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bob Marley",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the most famous reggae singer?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hotel California",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "From where can you check out anytime you like, but never leave?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Vain",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Fill in the blank: You're so ____ you probably think this song is about you"
  }, {
    "answer": "Osmond",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What was the last name of siblings Donny and Marie?"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Village People",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What band was composed of a cop, a soldier, a construction worker, a cowboy, a biker, and a Native American?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Diana Ross",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Which singer left The Supremes to start a successful solo career?"
  }, {
    "answer": "American Pie",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What song was inspired by \"The Day the Music Died\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Elvis Presley",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What rhinestone-studded singer frequently performed in Las Vegas?"
  }, {
    "answer": "AC/DC",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What Australian hard rockers did dirty deeds dirt cheap?"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Dark Side of the Moon",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What album by Pink Floyd charted for 741 consecutive weeks, starting in 1973?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Freebird",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What song by Lynyrd Skynyrd became the most-requested song of all time at concerts?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jim Morrison",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Whose grave in Paris has become a popular tourist attraction?"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Sex Pistols",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What band called the Queen a \"fascist regime\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Margaritaville",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Jimmy Buffet search for his lost shaker of salt?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Elton John",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who did Bernie Taupin collaborate with?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Barbra Streisand",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Who sang \"The Way We Were\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Punk",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What genre of music was CBGB famous for?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Convoy",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What #1 hit of 1975 was about a bunch of truckers talking on their C.B. radios?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Stairway to Heavan",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What rock song is performed with a double neck guitar",
  }, {
    "answer": "My Ding-a-Ling",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "What is Chuck Berry's only number-one single",
  }, {
    "answer": "Willie Nelson",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Which country music star is known for his braided hair",
  }, {
    "answer": "The Ramones",
    "category": "1970's Music Trivia",
    "question": "Whih punk rock band sang Blitzkreig Bop",
  }],
  "quizLength": 20,
  "title": "1970's Music Trivia",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/1970s-music-trivia"
}